Oh, hey! How was your audition?
試鏡如何？
I'm sorry, do I know you?
對不起，我認識你嗎？
What are you doing?
你在幹嘛？
Practicing blowing you off. I'm gonna be a big movie star!
練習假裝不認識你 我要成為電影明星了！
You got it?
你得到那個角色了？
-Not yet, but the audition went great! -What's it for?
-還沒，但試鏡很成功！ -什麼樣的角色？
A big-budget period movie about three Italian brothers...
大成本製作 關於三個意大利兄弟…
who come to America at the turn of the century. It's classy.
在世紀之初來到美國 是個經典故事
The director's supposed to be the next-next Martin Scorsese.
導演被認為是 下下個馬丁史柯西斯
The "next-next"?
「下下個」？
A guy from Chicago's supposed to be the next Martin Scorsese.
芝加哥的那個傢伙被認為是 下一個馬丁史柯西斯
This guy's right after him.
這個導演在他之後
Hello?
喂？
Joey, it's Estelle. I just talked to the casting people. They loved you!
喬伊，我是艾思拉，剛和選角的談過 他們很喜歡你！
They loved me!
他們很喜歡我！
They want to see you again tomorrow.
他們明天要再見你一次
-My God! -There's just one thing.
-我的天！ -只有一個問題
Do you have a problem with full-frontal nudity?
你對正面全裸有問題嗎？
Are you kidding me? I never rent a movie without it!
你開玩笑嗎？我從沒租過 一部沒有正面全裸的電影！
Oh.
哦
Okay, let me call you back.
好，我再回你電話
-What's the matter? -They want me naked in the movie.
-怎麼回事？ -電影裡需要我全裸
-Wow! -I know.
-哇！ -是啊
-My grandmother's gonna see this. -Grandma's gonna have to get in line.
-我祖母會看到的 -祖母還得排隊咧
The One With Ross and Monica's Cousin
本集播出：羅斯和摩妮卡的表妹
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
The wedding's so close. Are you nervous?
婚禮就快到了 你緊張嗎？
Yeah, but I also can't wait till it's over.
是啊，我等不及它結束
We have a pact not to have sex again until the wedding.
我們決定婚禮前不做愛的
A "no sex" pact, huh?
「無性」條約，嗯？
I have one of those with every woman in America.
我和全美每位女性 都有一份這個合約
Will you give me a hand making up the guest bedroom?
你能幫我整理客房嗎？
Cousin Cassie's staying with us for a few days.
凱西要來和我們住幾天
Cassie? I haven't seen her in, like, forever.
凱西？我很久沒看到她了
I wonder if she still carries a Barbie everywhere?
她是不是還帶著 芭比娃娃到處跑？
-She's 25 years old. -So? I still..
-她25歲了 -所以呢？我還是…
You're probably right.
你大概是對的
Phoebe, can I talk to you over here for a second?
菲比，我可以和你說句話嗎？
Subtle, guys.
要低調一點
What?
什麼？
I know you're planning my surprise bridal shower.
我知道你們在計劃 我的驚喜告別單身派對
Okay, well, don't ruin it. Just play along, at least.
好吧，別毀了它 至少假裝不知道
Okay. Sorry.
好，對不起
We have to throw her a shower?
我們要替她辦告別單身女子派對？
What'd you decide to do about the movie?
你決定那部電影該怎麼辦了嗎？
I don't know.
我不知道，我是說…
It's not like it's porn. This is a serious, legitimate movie.
那不是一部色情電影 這是一部嚴肅，正當的電影
Nudity's really important to the story.
這個故事裡的裸戲很重要
That's what you say about porn.
你也是這麼說色情電影的
Maybe I shouldn't go on the callback.
也許別去參加第二次試鏡
No, you should. A lot of major actors do nude scenes.
不，你應該去 很多大明星都有裸戲演出
The chance to star in a movie? Come on!
在電影裡演出的機會？拜託！
That's true. And I'm only naked in one scene. It sounds really great.
是真的，我只有一場裸戲 聽起來真的很不錯
My character's Catholic. He falls in love with a Jewish girl.
我的角色是個天主教徒 和一位猶太女孩戀愛了
We run away and get caught in a big rainstorm.
我們逃家而被陷在大雨中
We go into a barn, undress each other and hold each other.
躲到了穀倉裡 脫掉彼此衣服，抱在一起
It's really sweet and tender.
真的很甜蜜而溫柔
Plus, everyone will see your thing!
還有，每個人都看到你那話兒！
When can we have this shower?
我們何時能開這個告別單身女子派對？
She has so much going on,  we have only two options.
她有這麼多事要做 我們只有兩個選擇
-We have Friday. -That's just two days away.
-星期五 -只剩兩天了
-What is the other option? -Yesterday.
-另一個選擇是什麼？ -昨天
If we make it yesterday, we're done!
如果我們昨天就做好了 問題解決了！
It's impossible. We can't do this by Friday.
不可能 我們不可能在星期五辦
We have to find a place, invite people, get food.
要找到一個地點 邀請客人，買好食物
There's too much to do.
太多要做的
-We cannot do it! -Calm down!
-辦不到！ -鎮靜下來！
Okay. I'm sorry, you're right. I'm sorry.
好，抱歉，你是對的，抱歉
Just calm down, woman!
鎮靜下來，女人！
Phoebe, I already did.
菲比，我已經鎮靜下來了
All right, then I need to calm down.
好，那我需要鎮靜
I think we can do this if we just get organized.
有系統一點就能辦這件事
We have two days to plan this party. We need to make fast decisions.
有兩天來計劃這個聚會 做決定要快
Where will we have it?
要在哪裡辦？
-Here. What time? -4:00. Food?
-在這裡，什麼時間？ -4點正，食物？
-Finger sandwiches and tea. -Great! Very Monica.
-小三明治和茶 -好極了！很摩妮卡
-And chili! -You went one too far.
-還有辣椒！ -太過頭了
-Flowers or balloons? -Both.
-花還是氣球？ -兩個都要
-We're paying for this. -Neither.
-我們要付錢的 -兩個都不要
-What should we do for a theme? -Lusts of the Flesh!
-主題要什麼呢？ -肌夫之愛！
-What? -I don't know. Cowboy theme?
-什麼？ -我不知道，牛仔風？
I'm glad we decided not to sleep together before the wedding.
我很高興我們決定婚禮前不上床
Oh, boy. Me too.
我也是
I was thinking, say we had a big fight, and broke up for a few hours.
我在想，如果我們大吵一架 分手幾個小時
Technically, we could have sex again.
技術上來說，我們就可以上床
What do you think, bossy and domineering?
你說呢，頤指氣使的人？
The wedding's off, sloppy and immature.
婚禮取消了，不成熟的邋遢人
That's me. Come on.
我正是如此，走吧
Wait. Cassie's in the guest room. We're going to lunch.
等一下，凱西在客房 我們要出去吃中飯
Get rid of her, obsessive and shrill!
甩掉她，執拗尖銳的人！
Shrill? The wedding is back on.
尖銳？婚禮照常
I thought I heard voices. You must be Chandler.
我聽到有人講話 你一定是錢德
-Hi. Nice to meet you. -Nice to meet you too.
-很高興認識你 -很高興認識你
-So, ready to go? -Yeah.
-要走了嗎？ -好
-Chandler? -I'll be right with you.
-錢德？ -等一下
-Cassie needs to stay at your place. -Why?
-凱西必須去住你家 -為什麼？
Because "Pervie Perverson" here can't stop staring at her.
因為這位「變態人」 一直瞪著她看
Chandler, she's our cousin!
錢德，她是我們的表妹！
I wasn't staring. I was listening intently.
我沒有瞪著她看 我是很專心地聽她說話
It's called being a good conversationalist. Watch.
做一位好的聊天者，看著
Say something.
說話
You were staring about eight inches south of there.
你看著南面8公分外的地方
Fine. She can stay at my place.
好，她可以來住我家
What does Cassie look like now?
凱西現在長的什麼樣子？
Exactly like Aunt Marilyn.
就像瑪麗蓮阿姨
This Aunt Marilyn,  is she coming to the wedding?
瑪麗蓮阿姨會來參加婚禮嗎？
Wafer-thin ice.
你在薄冰上
Hey, I'm back.
我回來了
Hi, Joey.
喬伊
Will I read the same scene again?
我要念同一場戲嗎？
I tried to call you. You didn't need to come today.
我試著打電話給你 你今天不用來這兒
Oh, great.
太好了
I'd have been perfect for this part.
我會是這個角色的最佳人選
You made a bad decision and ruined your movie. Good day!
你錯誤的決定 會毀了你的電影，再見！
You didn't need to come, because the director saw your tape and loved it.
你不需要來這兒 因為導演看了你的帶子非常喜歡
End scene.
還有表演
Wasn't that fun? We did a little improv there. Yeah!
很好玩吧？剛剛的即席表演，！
So, you were saying?
你在說？
The director wants to meet you tomorrow.
導演明天想見你
Wow! Sure! That's great.
哇！當然！太好了
Your agent said you're okay with nudity.
你經紀人說你對裸戲沒問題
Yeah, sure. As long as it's handled tastefully.
是，只要很有格調地表現
And that barn is not too cold.
穀倉不要太冷
Perfect. There's one more thing.
好極了，還有一件事
It's important to the director that everything in the movie's authentic.
導演希望電影裡 每一樣事物都很正宗
In your love scene with Sarah...
你和莎拉的性愛場面…
she talks about how she's never seen a naked man who wasn't Jewish.
她說她從沒見過 不是猶太人的裸體男子
So...
所以…
So... what?
所以…怎樣？
So, the director is insisting that whoever play that part...
導演堅持演出這個角色的人…
be authentically, anatomically...
是正宗的，身體組織上…
not Jewish. You know what I'm saying?
不是猶太人 你知道我在說什麼？
Yes!
是！
No. What?
不，什麼？
An Italian Catholic immigrant at this time would not be....
在那時的意大利 天主教移民不會是…
Bar mitzvah-ed?
行過受誡禮的？
-To get this part, you can't be.. -No.
-要得到這個角色，你不能是… -不能
But you are?
可是你是？
-You told them you weren't? -That's right.
-你告訴他們你不是？ -對
Wow!
哇！
It's definitely all gone? There's nothing there to work with?
真的完全都沒有了？ 沒剩下一點可努力的餘地？
-What were you thinking? -I don't know. I just want this part.
-你在想什麼？ -我不知道，我想得到這個角色
They say no matter what you're asked during an audition, say yes.
他們說不管試鏡時問什麼 都回答是
They want you to ride a horse,  say you can.
如果要你騎馬，說你會
You figure out how to do it later.
之後再解決
This is not like learning to ride a horse. This is like learning to...
這和學會騎馬不一樣 這就像是學會…
grow a turtleneck.
長出高領衣的領子
I know, okay? Tomorrow, when I go meet the director...
我知道，好嗎？ 明天我去見導演時…
I have to take my clothes off so they can see what my body looks like.
我必須脫掉衣服 讓他們看我的身體
Oh, my God. What are you gonna do?
我的天，你要怎麼辦？
I have to call my agent and tell her I can't do the part.
必須打給我的經紀人 告訴她我不能接這個角色
Unless...
除非…
Unless what?
除非怎麼？
This may sound crazy, but there may be something we could...
聽起來很瘋狂 我們可能可以做點…
fashion.
造型
-Like what? -Well, I'm not sure yet.
-像什麼？ -我還不知道
Off the top of my head, I'm thinking...
隨便想想，我在想…
double-sided tape and some sort of luncheon meat.
雙面膠帶和某種午餐肉
I've got a great idea for party favors for the shower.
我有個派對主題的好主意
We get mahogany boxes and carve everyone's names in them.
用一個紅木箱 刻上每個人的名字
Then inside is each person's individual birthstone.
在裡面放著每個人的出生石
Okay. Okay.
好，好
You take care of that.
你來弄
Meanwhile, the party's tomorrow and we don't have a guest list.
同時，派對就在明天 我們還沒有賓客名單
Okay. Who do we know that's coming? Me. Are you?
好，我們知道要來的有誰？ 有我，你要來嗎？
-Hey. -Hey, what's up?
-嘿 -怎麼樣啊？
I'm making something for Joey. Can I raid your fridge?
我在替喬伊弄點東西 可以搜一下你的冰箱嗎？
Have at it.
請便
All right. Turkey? That won't work.
好，火雞肉？沒有用
Cheese? That won't work.
起司？沒有用
Olive loaf? I hope that won't work.
橄欖麵包，希望這沒用
Are you making him a sandwich?
你在替他做三明治嗎？
No, it's more like a wrap.
不，比較像是雞肉卷
Okay, so I'm gonna go, guys.
好，我要走了
So you can get back to deciding on what to get me for a present!
你們可以繼續討論 要送我什麼禮物！
We have to get her a present?
我們要送她禮物？
Okay, but look. Look at what I got.
好吧，看我拿到什麼
It's her address book. We have a guest list.
她的通訊錄 我們的賓客名單
You're amazing. Did you pull that out of her purse?
你好厲害，你從她皮包拿的？
Uh-huh. And a little seed money for the party.
嗯，還有派對的種子錢
Cassie?
凱西？
Hey, Ross!
羅斯！
It's been so long!
好久不見！
Last time I saw you...
上一次我看到你時…
you were setting up your tent in line for Return of the Jedi.
你正搭著帳篷 等待絕地武士的歸來
So you did see me that day. Because it seemed like you didn't.
所以那天你有看到我 看起來像沒看到的樣子
-Yeah, sorry about that. -It's okay. Come on in.
-對不起 -沒關係，請進
Thanks for letting me stay here. Monica's place was nice.
謝謝你讓我住在這兒 摩妮卡那兒不錯
But her fiance sure stares a lot.
但她的未婚夫一直瞪著人看
Oh, my God! You do a great Chandler!
我的天！你學錢德學得真像！
I have a knack for impressions.
我很會做表情的
Maybe after we get re-acquainted you could do me.
等我們熟一點 你也可以學我
Yeah. No!
好，不！
How you doing on that...
你的…
hot dog?
熱狗好吃嗎？
-I'm all done. -Thank God.
-我吃完了 -感謝上帝
The last time we hung out was when our parents rented that beach house.
上次見面是我們父母 租下海邊小屋那時
Remember the time I pinned you down and tickled you until you cried?
記得我按住你 搔你癢直到你哭了？
We're probably too old to do that now.
我們現在大了，不能這麼做了
I'll always remember that summer. It's when I got all these freckles.
我一直都記得那個夏天 我就是那時長了這些雀斑的
I'll always remember that summer...
我一直都記得那個夏天…
because that's when I realized that we are related.
因為那時我才知道我們是親戚
It took you that long to figure it out?
你花了那麼久才發現？
I'm a little slow.
我是有點反應遲緩
Just as our children would be.
就如我們的孩子也可能會這樣子
-Hi. -Hi.
-嗨 -嗨
How are you? Good. Hi. Thanks for coming.
你好嗎？好，嗨 謝謝大家來
Thank you. So nice to see you.
謝謝，很高興看到你
-No, thanks. -Okay. Hey, Rach?
-不，謝謝 -好，瑞秋？
-Yeah? -Who the hell are all these people?
-是？ -這些是什麼人啊？
I don't know. I called everybody in her book.
我不知道 我打給她本子裡的每一個人
These are the ones that could show up on 24 hours' notice.
這些是在24小時內通知還能來的
There's a word for people like that: Losers.
有另一個字來形容這種人：輸家
Hi, I'm Rachel. This is Phoebe. I'm the maid of honor.
我是瑞秋，這是菲比 我是伴娘
-How do you know Monica? -I was her accountant four years ago.
-你怎麼認識摩妮卡的？ -我是她四年前的會計師
I'm interested to find out who's been doing her taxes the last four years.
我很想知道 這過去四年是誰替她報稅
That's great.
很好
-When is Monica supposed to get here? -I don't know.
-摩妮卡何時會到？ -我不知道
Excuse us.
借一步說話
-You didn't tell her? -You were supposed to.
-你沒告訴她？ -你該通知她的
You were supposed to tell her to come! I was bringing the cake!
是你該通知她來的！ 我要帶蛋糕！
-Fine, I'll go call her. -And please tell her to bring a cake!
-好，我打電話給她 -要她帶蛋糕來！
We have a lot of options. A number of prototypes for you to try on.
我們有很多選擇 有幾個雛型可以試穿
Those look great.
看起來很好
Okay, this one's a mushroom cap. This one is made of bologna.
這個有磨菇做的頭 這個是意大利香腸做的
-The toothpicks? -Just until the glue dries.
-牙籤？ -只是撐著等膠水乾掉
Thank God.
感謝上帝
These are more realistic, but perishable.
這些比較逼真，但會腐爛
Over here, we have pink suede, which is nice.
這兒，粉紅色的鞣皮，很不錯
But if it gets wet, it'll shrink.
但濕了會縮水
Maybe we'll just take that one away.
把這個拿走好了
I also did a little something in fur, but that's really just for me.
我也做了一個毛的 不過那是給我自己的
Why don't you try these on? We'll get a better idea of what works.
不如你去試試這些？ 我們就知道哪些有用
Thanks, you are such a good friend. And this is so weird.
謝謝，你真是位好朋友 這真是奇怪透頂
-Toothpick? -Yeah.
-牙籤的？ -是
-What are you trying now? -The Fruit Roll-up.
-你現在在試那個？ -水果卷
-And? -Delicious.
-然後呢？ -很好吃
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. We have a winner!
等一下，等一下 冠軍出線了！
What? Which one?
怎樣？哪一個？
The Silly Putty. Not so silly anymore!
笨油灰不再那麼笨了！
She's your cousin. She's your cousin.
她是你表妹 她是你表妹
If she knew what was going on in your head, she'd think you were sick.
如果她知道你腦袋裡在想什麼 她會以為你有病
Or would she? Let's back up for a second.
她會嗎？ 倒轉一下
She was the one who suggested opening a bottle of wine.
是她提議開紅酒的
She was the one who turned down the lights.
是她把燈光調暗的
She was the one that wanted to rent Logan's Run...
是她要租《二十三世紀大逃亡》的…
the sexiest movie ever.
有史以來最性感的電影
I know that look.
我知道這眼神
Forget it. I want it. She wants it.
不管了，我想要，她想要
I'm going in.
我要行動了
What the hell are you doing?
你在幹什麼？
Say something clever.
說點機智的
Okay, doesn't have to be clever.
好吧，不必機智的
Just has to be words. Say some words.
只要說點什麼，說話
Any words will do.
什麼話都好
Oh, my God, this is the longest...
我的天，這是有史以來…
that anyone has not talked ever!
最長的沉默！
There is nothing you could say to make this worse...
說什麼都不可能讓情形更糟…
so just say something!
說點什麼！
I haven't had sex in a very long time.
我很久沒做愛了
Yeah, you really shouldn't have said anything.
你真的不該說話的
Phoebe? Rachel? It's Monica.
菲比？瑞秋？是摩妮卡
I wonder what you could possibly need me for on such short notice?
什麼事這麼急著找我來呢？
-Oh, Monica. We are so sorry. -For what?
-摩妮卡，我們很抱歉 -為什麼？
First, for forgetting to throw you a bridal shower.
第一，忘了替你辦告別單身女子派對
Then, forgetting to invite you to it.
然後忘了邀請你
You already had it?
你們已經辦完了？
We called everyone in your phone book. A bunch of people came.
我們打電話給你通訊錄裡每一個人 來了很多人
It took us so long to get you here that they had to leave.
但花了太多時間找到你 客人都走了
We wanted to throw you a big surprise and a great shower.
我們想給你一個大驚喜 替你辦一個大的告別單身女子派對
Now you don't have either.
現在兩個都沒了
We ruined everything.
我們毀了一切
No, wait a minute, that's not true. What you did was really sweet.
不，等一下，沒有毀了一切 你們真的很好心
-It kind of works out for the best. -What do you mean?
-其實這樣子最好 -什麼意思？
Now I get to spend my shower with the only people I really love.
現在我可以和我真正喜歡的人 一起共渡我的告別單身女子派對
I get all those presents without talking to people I don't even like!
我收了所有的禮物 而不必和我不喜歡的人說話！
-Surprise. -Surprise, Monica.
-驚喜 -驚喜，摩妮卡
What's cool is, the character is from Naples, right?
最酷的是，這個角色是從尼泊爾來的
My whole family's from Naples.
我全家都是從尼泊爾來的
That's great. Okay. I've heard everything I need to hear...
太好了，我聽得差不多了…
We just need to, uh...
我們只需要…
Leslie?
萊斯莉？
-Joey, this is the awkward part. -Hey, right. Not a problem.
-喬伊，這有點怪怪的 -是，沒有問題
I totally understand you need to...
我完全瞭解…
make sure I don't have any horrible scars or tattoos.
你們需要能確定 我沒有可怕的疤痕或刺青
Don't you worry.
不用擔心
I have nothing to hide.
我沒什麼要隱藏的
So, there you go. That's me.
這兒，這就是我
One hundred-percent natural.
百分之百純天然
I tell you, that has never happened before.
這從來沒發生過
Cassie, are you finding everything okay?
凱西，一切都還好嗎？
Yeah. Thanks for letting me stay here.
是，謝謝你讓我住這兒
Oh, it's no problem.
沒問題
What?
怎麼？
Say something. Say anything.
說話，隨便說什麼
Ask her out! She's not your cousin!
約她出去！她不是你表妹！